

# ABDALLAH KASHTA

Web Developer / Multimedia artist

#### **About Me**

Bringing over five years of diverse freelance experience in multimedia arts, content creation, and web development. Transitioning to a dedicated role in web development to drive innovation in digital spaces, echoing my adaptability and commitment displayed across various trades and roles

- <u>abdallahkashta.me</u>
- +64 9670212417
- abdallahkashta0@gmail.com
- 469 Manuel L. Quezon, Taguig - Metro Manila

#### Language

- Arabic
- English (intermediate)
- Tagalog (basic)

#### Expertise

- Creativity
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Interpersonal skills
- Team work
- Problem Solving

#### Experience

#### Multimedia artist

Taguig - Philippines / Cairo - Egypt 2019 - 2024

Over 5 years of freelance experience in multimedia arts, my skills and potential give me a significant advantage in modern-day trends and technology. my skills includes, graphic design, video editing, photoshop.

#### **Content Creation**

Taguig - Philippines / Cairo - Egypt 2021 - 2024

Proficient in content creation leveraging expertise from diverse locations. Demonstrated success in harnessing the power of content creation for unlocking present and future opportunities in my field.

### Web Development

2023 - 2024

During my studies in IT, I gained practical experience developing multiple websites utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP (2023-2024). Eager to expand my skills further and achieve success as a web developer.

#### Education

National University - Manila Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2020 - 2024

My excellence in academic activites lead to success and climbing into dean's list multiple times

#### Skills Summary

Multimedia Arts	67%
Content Creation	85%
Graphic Design	78%
Web Development	55%
Video Editing	85%





CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION

This certificate is awarded to

### Abdallah Kashta

For being an active participant in

#GENERATION HIRED

CONNECTING EDUCATION TO EMPLOYMENT

this November 23, 2023 in partnership with National University

Given this 5th of December, 2023

Erica Pascual

Marketing & Growth Supervisor







## CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

THIS CERTIFIES THAT

# Abdalla M. Ahmed Mohyeldin

has completed the training program for New Real Estate Salespersons on

REAL ESTATE BROKERAGE: RESA/IRR		credit units
CODE OF ETHICS		credit units
TAXATION (TRAIN LAW RA 8424)		credit units
REAL PROPERTY TAXATION		credit units
DOCUMENTATION AND TITLING PROCESS	2.0	credit units

Credit hours: 12 units Course completed on: July 16, 2023 Program Accreditation No.:

Date of conduct: July 14-16, 2023 Control No.: BL TMDC CX2T U5E5 7RRQ 2023-029-1439

TRAINING VENUE: ONLINE PLATFORM

REAL ESTATE CENTRE BLDG. 10 NARRA ST. GEV, PASIG CITY



MARIA TERESITA CANLAS

**PRESIDENT** 





## **CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST CERTIFICATE**

Presented to

Abdalla Mohyeldin

Given on May 2023 for successfully completing the Customer Service Test provided by Mangtas.

THANK YOU FOR YOUR STELLAR PERFORMANCE!





REFERENCE NO: 3161101



awards this

# Certificate of Recognition

to

# Kashta, Abdallah Mohammed

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology with Specialization in Multimedia Arts & Animation Dean's Second Honor List, 3.38 GWA 1<sup>st</sup> Term, AY 2021-2022

Given this 6th day of December 2021 at National University, Manila.

Arlene O. Trillanes

Dean, College of Computing and Information Technologies

Marc Rey D. Salido

Director, Student Development & Activities Office



awards this

# Certificate of Recognition

to

# KASHTA, ABDALLAH MOHAMMED

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology with Specialization in Multimedia Arts and Animation Dean's Second Honor List, 3.30 GWA 1st Term, AY 2020-2021

Given this 11th day of January 2021 at National University, Manila.

Arlene O. Trillanes

Dean, College of Computing and Information Technologies

Marc Rey D. Galido
Director, Student Affairs Office